Guide to the Hoover Institution Archives Photograph Card Catalog
Hoover Institution Archives
- Foss (Fedor F.) Collection, 395 prints / 13 negatives / 21 envelopes / 3 albums (Box 36006 - 10.A-V)
  - 7 prints depicting scenes at the All-Russian Exposition, Nizhnii-Novgorod, 1896 (Folder mM)
  - 5 prints depicting the Lyssva Mining District and Lys'venskii Zavod pavilion at the Architectural Exhibition, St. Petersburg, 1910, and the booth at Iron and Steel Exhibition, St. Petersburg, 1903 (Folder mN)
  - 22 prints, 1 negative, depicting Count Paul P. Shuvalov, proprietor of the Lys'venskii Zavod, and the erection of his monument after his death in 1901 (Folder mO)
  - 16 prints, 1 negative, depicting buildings, staff, machinery and surrounding area of the Sormovo Works and Prince Khilikov, 1897-1900 (Folder mP)
  - SAME AS ABOVE, 10 prints, 2 negatives, undated (Box 36006 - 10.A-V, Folder mQ)
  - 10 prints depicting buildings, machinery, staff and surrounding area of the Sormovo Works, 1897-1900 (Folder mR)
  - SAME AS ABOVE, 9 prints, undated (Folder mS)
  - SAME AS ABOVE, 8 prints, undated (Folder mT)
  - 4 prints, 1 negative, depicting the Baltic Government Navy Yard and 1 print depicting the People's House in Petrograd, undated (Folder mU)
  - Album with 43 prints depicting various Russian ethnical types at the turn of the century, undated (Folder fV)
  - Album with 19 prints depicting places of interest in Kiev, undated (Folder fW)
  - Album with 40 prints depicting places of interest in Kiev, undated (Box 36006 - 10.A-V, Folder fX)
  - 8 oversize photos depicting Shuvalov's monument, the Lyssva Mining District, F. F. Foss, and Lys'Venskii Zavod, undated (Folder m*)
- Foto-Willinger Collection, 1919-1945; 64 envelopes (Box XX225 - 10.A Envelope A-BL)
  Photographs depicting scenes of daily life in Germany in the interwar period and during World War II, including the social cultural, industrial, and agricultural activities. Also includes scenes of Nazi activities and of military operations during World War II. Photographs are mostly positives with some negatives. See Black Binder for detailed description.
- France. Ministere De La Guerre. Section Photographique De L'Armee. Collection, undated; 32 prints / 1 album (Box 89041 - 8M.02 Album fA)
  Depicts arrival of American troops in France in World War I. Includes photographs of General John Pershing and Marshal Ferdinand Foch.
- Frank (Colman D.) Collection, circa 1918-21.; 7 prints and 1 lithograph / 1 envelope (Box 62005 - 10.V)
  4 prints depicting members of the Permanent International Armistice Commission for W.W. I, including photos of Pershing and C.D. Frank; 1 print depicting F. Foch, L. Loucheur, R. Poincare, G. Clemenceau, and Leygues; one lithograph of R. Nivelle; 2 prints depicting French troops in Alsace-Lorraine.
- Frank, Karl (Pseud.: Paul Hagen) Collection, 1946; 10 prints / 1 envelope (Box 71044 - 10.A-V)
  8 photographs of K. Frank alone or with wife or friend; 1 portrait of Johann Lenk, 1 portrait of Robert Heckert.
- Frederick (Robert T.) Collection, 80 prints / 3 envelopes and 1 album (Box 68009 - 10 A-V)
  - 1 album of 34 photos of scenes at the German concentration camp at Dachau following its liberation by the allies. Album includes a history of the camp, undated (Folder fA)
  - 1 photo of U.S. soldiers at the Dachau concentration camp during its liberation, undated (Folder B)
  - 5 aerial photos of landings of the First Airborne Task Force in So. France near Le Muy, August 15, 1944 (Folder C)
  - 40 prints depicting the T-15 Light Cargo Carrier and U.S. military personnel in France and Germany, 1945 (Folder D)
- Free, Arthur M. Collection, undated; 80 prints / 8 envelopes (Box m33007 -10.AV)
  - 35 prints of German troops in Belgium and France and of war scenes on the western front during World War I, undated (Folder mA)
  - 18 prints of German troops and war scenes on the Eastern front during World War I, undated (Folder mB)
  - 5 prints of troops of the Central Powers on the Italian front and in Turkey during World War I, undated (Folder mC)
  - 8 prints of German airplanes, fliers, ships, and seamen during World War I, undated (Folder mD)
  - 4 prints of Allied soldiers captured by German troops during World War I, undated (Folder mE)
  - 4 prints of Kaiser Wilhelm II and Crown Prince Wilhelm of Germany visiting the Western front, undated (Folder mF)
  - 1 print of Prince Max of Baden; 1 print of General Paul von Hindenburg; 1 print of General Pavlo Skoropads'kii, hetman of the Ukraine, undated (Folder mG)
  - 7 prints of scenes at the Brest-Litovsk Treaty negotiations with the Ukraine, members of the Central Powers' delegations (including Richard von Kuehlmann and General Max Hoffmann of Germany, Count Ottokar von Czernin of Austria, and Talaat Pasha of Turkey), and members of the Ukrainian delegation (including N. Liubyns'kyi, N. Levyts'kyi Aleksandr Sevriuk and Serhii Ostapenko), undated (Folder mH)
- Freeman, Joseph Collection, 914 prints, 31 postcards, 2 negatives, 49 duplicates, 22 slides / 40 envelopes, 1 album, 1 slide box (Box 80159 - Photo file)
- Friedland (William Collection), 3 prints / 3 negatives / 3 envelopes (Box 69042 - 9.15)
  - 1 print of Sheha Amiri and Victor Mkello, 1963 (Folder A)
  - 1 print of Sheha Amiri, 1963 (Folder B)
  - 1 print of Victor Mkello, 1963 (Folder C)
- Friedman, Milton Collection, 6 prints / 1 envelope (Box 77011 - Photo File Envelope A)
  3 prints depicting Milton Friedman during his appearances on the television program Meet the Press in 1976 and 1978; 2 print depicting him with others in 1978; and 1 print depicting him with James McClune and Joseph Pichler following his talk in Kansas City, Missouri, on December 4, 1975.
- Frillmann, Paul W. Collection, undated; 164 prints / 8 negatives / 3 envelopes / 1 oversize box (Box 75056 - 10.A-V and 75056 - 8M.02)
  - 7 prints of Paul W. Frillmann; 9 prints of Paul W. Frillmann and others; 30 prints of Paul W. Frillmann officiating at American Volunteer Group (Flying Tiger) funerals; 5 prints of American Volunteer Group burials; 2 prints of cemetery where American Volunteer group members are buried, undated (Folder A)
  - 31 prints of unidentified scenes; 65 prints of unidentified people; 8 negatives, undated (Folder B)
  - 10 prints of portraits of American Volunteer Group members; 2 prints of American Volunteer Group members; 2 prints of General Claire L. Chennault; 1 print of General Claire L. and Mrs. Anna Chennault with unidentified person, undated (Folder C)
  - 1 photograph album, primarily prints of Chinese paintings; 1 picture of Paul W. Frillmann on woodblock, undated (Folder fD)
- Fuhrman, Frederick E. Collection, 1918-1919; circa 700 prints / 6 envelopes (Box 87029 - 10.A-V)
  Scenes along the Trans-Siberian Railroad and Chinese Eastern Railway in Siberia and Manchuria during the Russian Civil War. Including troops and civilians of various nationalities, and railroad stock.
- Fuller, Benjamin Apthorp Gould Collection, 91 prints / 2 envelopes (Box XX095 - 10.AV)
  - 15 prints depicting ceremonies surrounding the conferral of the baton of Marshal of France to General Ferdinand Foch, including photos of Poincare, Loucheur, Clemenceau, Leygues, and Weygand, August 28, 1918 (Folder A)
  - 76 prints depicting activities of the Peace Conference at Versailles, including photos of the French, British, Italian, and American representatives, military and diplomatic, 1919 (Folder B)
- Fuller, William Parmer Collection, 333 prints / 174 negatives / 5 envelopes / 3 oversize boxes (Box 57007 - 10.A-V, 57007 - 8M.02)
  See preliminary inventory for list of photographs.
- Furlong, Charles W. Collection, 402 photographs / 8 envelopes (Box 63017 - 10.A-V)
  - 1 print of President Woodrow Wilson and Marine Guard; 1 print of Woodrow Wilson and Adm. Grayson; 1 print of Maj. C.W. Furlong and others; 1 print of Dean Haskins, J.J. Jusserand, Henry White; Gen. M. Churchill, Isaiah Bowmand, and C.W. Furlong; 1 print of Amb. Macchi de Celleri; 1 print of Amb. Henry White; 1 print of William Bullitt; 1 print of Woodrow Wilson;1 print of C.W. Furlong, Dr. Mezies, Col. Ayres and others; 1 print of Pres. and Mrs. Wilson, 1 print of Gen. John J. Pershing, Joffre and Raymond Poincare; 1 print of George Creel; 1 print of Robert Lansing; 1 print of Pres. Wilson and crew of U.S.S. George Washington; 1 print of Pres. and Mrs. Wilson disembarking; 1 print of Mr. and Mrs. John Davis; 1 print of Maj. C. W. Furlong; 23 prints on board U.S.S. George Washington enroute to Paris, December 4-13, 1918; 1 miscellaneous print of the Dartmouth College lounge (Folder A)
  - 4 prints of Woodrow Wilson; 3 prints of Woodrow Wilson and others on tour in France; 1 print of Woodrow Wilson and Gen. John J. Pershing; 1 print of Woodrow Wilson, Robert Lansing, David Lloyd-George, Gen. Tasher Bliss, and unidentified person; 1 print of Woodrow WIlson and Pres. Raymond Poincare; 1 print of Pres. and Mrs. Woodrow Wilson and others; 1 print of Woodrow Wilson, David Lloyd-George, Vittorio Orlando, Georges Clemenceau; 1 print of Woodrow Wilson, Adm. Grayson, and others; 1 print of Gen. John J. Pershing and others; 1 print of Brig. Gen. M. Churchill and Mr. Mezies; 1 print of Pres. and Mrs. Raymond Poincare; 1 print of Edward house; 1 print of Col. Van Dieman; 1 print of Woodrow Wilson; 7 postcards of Woodrow Wilson and Peace Conference leaders; 17 prints of scenes at the Paris Peace Conference, 1919 (Folder B)
  - 1 print of Gen. John J. Pershing, Major Shallenberger, Gen. W. Lassiter, Mr. Cox; 1 print of Freyre-Santander, Gen. Pershing, and Augustin Edwards; 1 print of Lt. Casanova; 1 print of Gen. John J. Pershing and others; 1 print of Isolina and Elsa Herrera; 1 print of Gen. John J. Pershing, Augustin Edwards, Dr. Freyre-Santander; 1 print of Augustin Edwards and others; Amb. Poindexter and others; 53 prints of people and scenes taken in Tacna-Arica during C.W. Furlong's membership in the American commission sent to arbitrate, circa 1926 (Folder C)
  - 1 print of Cap. Guynemer; 4 prints of Verdun; 2 prints of British tanks; 3 prints of German ships; 3 prints of aerial warfare; 2 prints of the trenches; 3 miscellaneous prints on the European War, 1914-1918 (Box 63017 - 10.A-V, Folder D)
  - 2 prints of C.W. Furlong and others; 1 print of Archduke Francis Ferdinand and his wife; 1 print of Furlong and Flora Sands; 1 print of Furlong and others; 1 print of Gen. Graziolli; 1 print of Senor and Senora Valerio Benuzzi and others; 1 print of Col. Everson; 1 print of Alice Sustersic; 3 prints of Furlong, Alice Sustersic and others; 1 print of Gen Sasi; 1 print of Gen. Graziolli; 1 print of Furlong, Mr. and Mrs. Desorski and Mrs. Desorski's sister; 2 prints of Gen. Graziolli and staff; 1 print of Furlong and others; 1 print of Radoica Nikchevich and others; 1 print of King Nicholas of Montenegro; 1 print of Marko Z. Popovich; 2 prints Furlong and unidentified man; 1 print of Furlong and others; 1 print of Lawrence Brown and others; 1 print of Lawrence Brown and others; 1 print of Furlong and unidentified man; 1 print of Lawrence Brown; 1 print of Gen. Andriya Raichevich, Maj. Djuro Yovovich, Stevan Pavlovich, Lt. Djucan Vukmanovich, Capt. Djuro Kapichich; 1 print of Radojico Vikcevic; 1 print of Commandante Ernesto Burzagli; 4 prints of King Nicolas and others; 2 prints of Raioska Nickovic and Montenegrin guerrillas; 2 prints of Furlong and others; 1 print of Prince Milo of Montenegrin guerillas; 2 prints of Furlong and others; 1 print of Prince Milo of Montenegro; 1 print of Adm. Andres; 4 unidentified prints; 14 prints of Austro-Hungarian atrocities against the Yugoslavs; 23 prints of Fiume (Rijeka), undated (Folder E)
  - 1 print of bust of Woodrow Wilson; 1 print of Augustin Edwards, Gen. John J. Pershing, Col. R.E. Kreager, Dr. M. de Freyre and staff members of the Tacna-Arica Commission, undated (Folder mF)
- Gaffney (T. St. John) Collection, 1932; 1 print / 1 envelope (Box 42008 - 10.A-V)
  1 print of the German Kaiser Wilhelm II., autographed and presented by the emperor to Mr. Gaffney.
- Gajda, Rudolf Collection, undated; 280 prints / 1 album (Box 92021 - 8M.02 album fA)
  280 prints depicting Czechoslovak, White Russian and Allied troops in Siberia during the Russian Civil War.
- Galpin, Perrin C. Collection, 27 photographs / 2 envelopes (Box 57015 -9.13)
  - 10 photographs depicting Herbert Hoover on his trip to Europe on board of SS Normandie and in Belgium, accompanied by Perrin C. Galpin and Paul C. Smith, 1938 (Folder A)
  - 17 photographs depicting Herbert Hoover on his trip to Europe and Asia, at the Vatican, in Poland, Greece and Norway, 1946 (Folder B)
- Galvin (John A.T.) Collection, undated; 1 envelope (Box 55004 - 10 A-V)
  Reproductions of paintings, depicting scenes from the Franco-Prussian War, the Boxer Rebellion, and the Russo-Japanese War, including the battle of Tsushima Straits. Also includes miscellaneous scenes, mainly of Japan.
- Gann, Lewis H. Collection, undated; 1 print / 1 envelope (Box 72101 - Photo file Envelope A)
  1 print depicting Lewis H. Gann.
- Gavrilovic, Milan Collection, undated; 69 prints / 4 envelopes (Box 76072 - 10.A-V)
  - 14 prints depicting Milan Gavrilovic and others, undated (Folder A)
  - 16 prints depicting unidentified individuals, family members, and various homes, undated (Folder B)
  - 28 prints depicting various individuals associated with M. Gavrilovic, undated (Folder C)
  - 11 prints of Branislaw Stanisic, undated (Folder D)
- Gavronsky, J. O. Collection, undated; 16 prints, 1 envelope (Box 89029 - 10.A-V Envelope A)
  14 prints of Alexander Kerensky on the south-western Russian military front in 1917; 1 print of Kerensky playing with children, 1919; and 1 print of Kerensky together with others members of the Comite pour la Russie in Paris in 1920.
- Gazeta Wyborcza Collection, 1989-1992; 238 prints / 13 envelopes (Box 92114 - 10.A-V)
  213 prints depicting scenes of political and social conditions in Poland following the fall of the communist regime. Includes portraits of political leaders, scenes of protest movements, and scenes of religious activities.
- German American Bund Collection, 1936-1941; 17 negatives / 1 envelope (Box 72104 - 10.A-V)
  Photographs of Fritz Kuhn and other leaders of the German American Bund, including photographs of them with Adolf Hitler; and photographs of activities of the Bund.
- Germany. Heer. Infanterie-Regiment 163 Collection, 1914-1918; 1 album / 1 manuscript box (Box fXX455 - 8.24)
  Photos depicting officers and men of Infanterie-Regiment 163 of the German Army and scenes of their activity in campaigns in France and Belgium during World War I.
- Gesamtverband Deutscher Antikommunistischer Vereinigungen Collection, 1914-1939 (Box XX090 - 8M.31/32 Box 215-221)
  Photographs depicting prominent communists and Jews from several countries, including political figures, writers, musicians, scientists; scenes of Jewish artistic life, particularly theater life; and scenes of daily life and military operations in Germany and the Soviet Union. Includes some caricatures and cartoons.
- Gesellschaft Fuer Kulturellen Austausch Mit Dem Ausland Collection, undated; 10 envelopes (Box XX252 - 10.A-V)
  - Photographs relating to social and economic conditions in Cottbus, East Germany, and to the life of Wilhelm Pieck, 1923-1960 (Folder A)
  - Photographs relating to social and economic conditions in East Germany. Captions are in Italian, undated (Folder mB-I)
  - Photographs relating to social and economic conditions in East Germany. Captions are in Italian, undated (Folder mJ dr. 4)
- Geyer, Georgie Anne Collection, 100 prints / 3 envelopes (Box 91037 - 10.A-V)
  - 96 prints of locations in Mexico City, primarily street scenes and buildings, associated with Fidel Castro and Jose marti, 1986 (Folder A-C)
  - 2 prints of the Belen Jesuit School, Havana and Miami; 2 prints of the Huber Matos, Jr. family, 1986 (Folder C)
- Gibson, Herbert Daskum Collection, 1932; 2 prints / 1 envelope (Box m82024 - 10.A-V Envelope mA)
  Depicts a U.S. Army horse show team in the Philippine Islands.
- Gibson, Hugh S. Collection, 496 prints, 4 booklets of prints, 76 postcards, 4 negatives (Box 56000-10.A-V)
- Gilinsky, Victor Collection, 53 prints / 3 envelopes (Box 82091 - 10.A-V)
  - 38 prints of clean-up procedures at Three Mile Island (?); 8 prints of a damaged facility; 1 print of the La Hague plant, undated (Folder A)
  - 5 prints of construction of the Shearon Harris plant, 1980 (Folder mB)
  - 1 print of Iraklii G. Tsereteli with Viktor M. Chernov and his wife, circa 1950 (Folder C)
- Gitlow, Benjamin Collection, 2 prints, 1 drawing / 1 envelope (Box 67031 - 10.A-V Envelope A)
  Two photographs of striking silk workers, Paterson, New Jersey, 1931; and 1 miscellaneous drawing.
- Glotzer, Albert Collection, undated; 69 prints / 6 envelopes (Box 91006 - 10.A-V)
  - 13 prints of Leon Trotsky, 1930s. (Folder A)
  - 4 prints of Leon Trotsky with others, including his wife, daughter, son Lev Sedov, Charles Curtiss, and Abraham and Roman Sobolevicius, 1930s (Folder B)
  - 6 prints of Leon Trotsky and Albert Glotzer and the Trotsky residence in Kadikoy, Turkey, 1931 (Folder C)
  - 35 prints of Leon Trotsky, Albert Glotzer and others at hearings of the Commission of Inquiry into Charges Made against Leon Trotsky in the Moscow Trials, Coyoacan, Mexico. Persons depicted include Carlton Beals, John Dewey, James T. Farrell, Jan Frankel, Albert Goldman, Friday Kahlo, Pearl Kluger, Suzanne LaFollette, John Mc Donald, George Novack, Diego Rivera, Otto Ruhle, Herbert Solow, Benjamin Stolberg, Nataliia Sedova Trotskaia, Jean van Heijenoort, and Bernard Wolfe, 1937 (Folder D)
  - 7 prints, including 3 relating to the Leon Trotsky assassination, 1 of Trotsky's grave, 1 of the Trotsky museum, and 2 of Diego Rivera murals depicting Trotsky and other communist leaders, undated (Folder E)
  - 4 prints, including 1 of Albert Glotzer with Gil Green, Max Shachtman and others, 1927; 1 of Walter Held, circa 1934; 1 of James P. Cannon and Max Shachtman, 1938; and 1 of Albert Glotzer with Nataliia Sedova Trotskaia, 1953 (Folder F)
- Godard (Yves) Collection, 17 photos / 5 x-ray negatives / 1 watercolor / 1 oversize postcard / 1 envelope (Box m76073 - 10.A-V)
  9 aerial reconnaissance photos taken over Indochina, January 1954; 1 group photo of Godard and a company of the 27th Bataillon de Chasseurs Alpins, 1935-36; 3 photos of Godard, 1939; 1 photo portrait of Godard 1946; 1 photo of Godard, undated; 1 oversize postcard of Algiers; 5 x-ray negatives of Godard's fractured leg, 1939; 1 watercolor of French Alpine Troops, 1944-45; 2 photos of Hussein-Dey police academy graduation ceremony, circa 1958-59.
- Goring (Hermann Wilhelm) Collection, 42 prints / plus 1 duplicate / 1 envelope (Box XX119 - 10.)
  42 prints depicting Goring, Hitler, Mussolini, and various Nazi officials. Berlin, Rome. 1930's and early 1940's.
- Golder, Frank Collection, undated; 124 prints /12 envelopes (Box XX058 - 10.A-V)
  - 4 prints of Frank Golder, circa 1928 (Folder A)
  - 1 print depicting the staff of the U.S. American Relief Administration, European Operations, office in Copenhagen, 1920 (Folder B)
  - 9 prints depicting U.S. American Relief Administration, Russian operations, staff in Russia and Soviet government officials, 1921-23 (Folder C)
  - 81 prints depicting conditions and victims of the famine in Russia, 1921-23 (Folder D-I)
  - 11 prints depicting cannibalism in Russia during the famine, 1921-1923 (Box J)
  - 1921-23, undated (Folder 10 prints depicting various scenes in Russia)
  - 8 prints depicting various scenes in Latvia and Lithuania, undated (Box L)
- Goodfellow, M. Preston Collection, 23 photographs / 3 negatives / 2 envelopes (Box 69085 - 10.A-V)
  - 2 prints of General John Hodge and others; 1 print of Gen. John Hodge and others. 1 print of M. Preston Goodfellow, Gen John Hodge and others; 1 print of John Kim; 1 print of Pres. Syngman Rhee; 1 print of Pres. Syngman Rhee and others; 1 print of M. Preston Goodfellow Pres. and Mrs. Syngman Rhee, and unidentified person; 1 print of Syngman Rhee and others; 1 print of Pres. Syngman Rhee at inaugural; 1 print of Myung Ki Hong; 1 print of Frederick Waller and Jiuji G. Kasai; 5 prints of scenes at Syngman Rhee inaugural; 1 print of Lord Louis Mountbatten, M. Preston Goodfellow, and Col. John H. Voegtly; 4 prints of gifts to President Franklin Roosevelt from Dalai Lama of Tibet, 1943; 1 unidentified print (Folder A)
  - Photo album of Frederick Waller, undated (Folder mB)
    Photo album of Frederick Waller.
- Goodman, Allan E. Collection, 44 prints, 23 negatives, 1 contact sheet, 2 watercolor paintings, 1 map / 7 envelopes (Box 75001 - 10.A-V)
  - Autographed portrait of Ellsworth Bunker, U.S. Ambassador to South Vietnam, 1970 (Folder A)
  - Color aerial view of Vietnam, undated (Box B)
  - Photo of Allan E. Goodman; photo of Sok Thong Doeung, Director, Research Dept., Technical University of Phnom Penh, 1970; photo of Allan E. Goodmanand other participants, U.S. Dept. of State Scholar-Diplomat Seminar for East Asian Affairs, Washington, D.C., Dec. 14-18, 1970, with explanatory letter (Folder C)
  - 23 negatives, 1 contact sheet and 7 prints of Lam Son Square, Saigon, with explanatory letter, undated (Box D)
  - 32 photos of missiles, airplanes radar installations and various scenes at headquarters and outlying posts of the North American Air Defense Command, undated (Box E)
  - 2 watercolor paintings of scenes of daily life in a South Vietnamese village, undated (Folder mF)
  - Mounted street map of Saigon, undated (Folder mG)
- Goodyear, Anson Conger Collection, 14 photographs / 3 envelopes (Box 56024 - 10.A-V)
  - 5 photos of other coal mines in Bohemia including one showing young women and child laborers, circa 1919 (Folder A)
  - 5 photos of other coal mines in Bohemia including one showing young women and child laborers, circa 1919 (Box B)
  - 4 photos from Bruex (Most) Coal Region, a photographed map of the region, a photographed watercolor of Alexander coal mine, views of 2 other coal mines, circa 1919 (Folder mC)
- Gorton (Willard L.) Collection, undated (Box XX167 - 9.23)
  - Places of religious worship and people, 57 prints and 3 negatives, undated (Folder A)
  - 95 prints and 25 negatives of the populace at work, undated (Box B)
  - 65 prints and 14 negatives of street scenes, populace, and scenery, undated (Folder C)
  - Western USSR and Europe: 96 prints and 130 negatives, undated (Box D)
- Gould, Randall Chase Collection, undated; 2 envelopes / 5 albums (Box 69086 - 10.A-V)
  - 2 prints of George Gould, 1 print of George Gould and others, 1 print of Mr. and Mrs. George Gould and Randall Gould, 4 prints of Randall Gould, 6 prints of Randall Gould and others, 2 prints of the Shanghai Evening Post and mercury building, 7 miscellaneous prints, undated (Folder A)
  - 5 albums of prints of the Japanese bombing of Shanghai, China, 1937 (Folder fB-F)
  - 16 prints depicting the execution of Chinese civilians by Japanese soldiers during the Sino-Japanese Conflict, 1937-1945 (Box G)
  - 1 album of prints of the Japanese bombing of Shanghai, 1937 (Folder fH)
- Green, Joseph C. Collection, undated; 30 photographs / 123 postcards / 2 envelopes (Box 56025 - 10.A-V)
  - 1 print of Joseph C. Green and others; 3 unidentified prints; 26 prints of industries, Liege, Belgium, undated (Folder A)
  - 123 postcards of Europe, circa 1917-1918 (Box B)
- Gregory (Thomas T. C.) Collection, undated; 4 prints / 2 envelopes / 1 photo album (Box 72059 - 10 A-V)
  - 2 photos of the Republican National Convention delegation sent to notify Hoover of his nomination as it leaves San Francisco in Hoover's presence and arrives in Kansas City, Mo, June, 1928 (Folder A dr. 3)